http://www.parkeryamaha.com/privacy-policy.aspx

800 S California Ave, Parker, AZ, 85344, Phone 928-669-2549
Open Mon-Sat 8am-5pm and Sunday 8am-3pm AZ Time.
AccessoriesATV, UTV PartsElectrical AccessoriesGeneratorsMarine PartsMotorcycle PartsOils and LubricantsPersonal Watercraft PartsSnowmobile PartsSport Boat PartsToolsTrailer PartsVehicle SalesView Store Pics
Credit Card PaymentsEmploymentInternational OrdersOrder StatusMSDS RequestParts Request FormPoliciesShipping Estimates
Select ...
303
Accel
AFI
Airhead Kwik Tek
Ancra
Aqua Cart
Aqua Performance
Aqua Torque
Parker Yamaha Com Home Page > Privacy Policy
Our Website Security is provided by the companies listed, Clicking on the Netseal above will verify Sitesafe.
Due to page load issues we have moved the live seal from our front page to this page.
Parker Yamaha, SeaDoo, Kawasaki, Polaris & Honda has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for these websites: Parkersportscenter.com, ParkerYamaha.com. ParkerYamaha.net
We agree not to share or sell your information. This information is collected for the sole purpose of our billing and shipping needs. All items on this web site are to be considered the property of GEI LLC, Dba Parker Yamaha, Parker Sports Center and and may not be used without prior authorization. We use outside companies (such as UPS, USPS, Fed Ex. etc.) to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not to our knowledge, retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site and for order form confirmation.
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Our site requires cookies enabled to use our forms for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information to process your order. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services and is not stored in your customer cart file. Cookies used in our site are to aid in your shopping and for our cart to work properly. You will need basic cookies enabled to purchase on our site.
Our online parts request form asks visitors for contact information (like their email address). We will use this data to reply to the information you requested. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor by us and only us when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
Our site uses the latest security protocols and maintains Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standards at all times. Secure elements on our site such as the shopping cart and checkout process utilize TLS 1.1 or TLS 1.2 security protocols.
If you are using an older device with either an insecure operating system or outdated browser that does not support either TLS 1.1 or TLS 1.2 you will need to upgrade your browser to check out at a PCI compliant website like ours.
Current TLS 1.1 and TLS 1.2 supported browsers include:
Chrome 30+
Android 5.0+
Firefox 27+
Internet Explorer 11 + (can be enabled on 8-10 -
Windows 7 / 8)
Edge Internet Explorer Mobile 11 (can be enabled on 10)
Opera 14+ (can be enabled on 8 - 12.7)
Safari 9 (OS X 10.9)
Safari Mobile 5+
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You will also have this option in your customer file.
To be removed from our current Emailing list please use the Remove Link on any News letter or email flyer you received on the provided link within that email. or contact us to be removed.
Correct/Update
This site gives users the options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
Or you may send mail to the following postal address:
Parker Yamaha
800 California Ave, Parker AZ 85344
Call the following telephone number: 928.669.2549
You can Fax us at: 928.669.6656
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,
Please contact us.
Parker Yamaha SeaDoo, Polaris & Honda
800 California Ave
Parker, AZ , 85344
Recently Viewed Products
Your cart is empty.
Email Address:
Password:
Remember Me
Create an account
Forgot Password?
BRP Parts FinderKawasaki Parts FinderPolaris Parts FinderYamaha Parts Finder
Battery TechCavitation PWCBirth Of SeaDooFuel Condition Q&AImpeller ChartImpeller TechMat InstallationsOil Q&AOff Season StoragePre Season TechPWC CoversWetsuit FactsBRP Instructions
Home | About Us | Contact Us | My Account | Shipping Policy | Policies | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | Cart Help
© 2020Parker Yamaha, SeaDoo, Polaris, Honda, Kawasaki
Mailorder OEM Parts & Accessories for SeaDoo, Polaris, Yamaha, Kawasaki, Can-Am, Honda, OEM Certified Dealer, Prices herein are not valid on walk-in or retail store sales and may vary from phoned in prices. Web or Mailorders cannot be picked up at store. We reserve the right to change prices without notice. A complete list of our policies can be viewed on our policy page. We are not responsible for errors relating to any product or prices listed herein and in no way offer to make restitution for any such errors. Any pictures herein may be for reference only and may not depict the actual part in some cases. Some orders may not ship the day your order was submitted. Our website does not list if items are in stock, Please do not ASSUME that if it is shown here we have it in stock and ready to ship since not all items shown herein are in stock and as such will be special ordered as needed to fill your order.
California Prop 65 WARNING:
Certain products for sale on this website can expose you to chemicals which are known
to the State of California to cause cancer, birth defects or reproductive Harm – www.P65Warnings.ca.gov
